5/417, Echanahalli, Rayakottai, Krishnagiri, Tamil Nadu-635116 + 91-9786146414 www.srajs.com

mailto:iam@srajs.com

RAJESH SIVASANKARAN

PROFILE SUMMARY

Having **3.9 years** of experience in analysis, design and development of windows, web and mobile based application.

Developing web and mobile applications in HTML, JavaScript, and jQuery, CSS, ASP.Net MVC, Angular, Ionic and Cordova.

Knowledge in .Net framework using **MVC** with Entity framework, Dapper and ADO.Net.

Knowledge in Stored Procedures and functions using SQL Server and MySQL.

Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams.

Code managing with Team Foundation Server (TFS) and GitHub.

A self-motivated person with ability to learn new technologies and adapt to new environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Core Skills	MVC, Angular, SQL
Technology	C#.NET, VB.Net, ASP.NET, MVC, Web Api, HTML, Angular, Ionic,
	Typescript, JavaScript, jQuery, PL/SQL.
App Servers	IIS, Wamp.
Databases	SQL Server, MySQL.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, Mindteck (India) Limited, Bengaluru, Karnataka.

http://mindteck.com/

Aug 2017 - Till

Software Engineer, Cogwave software Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Bengaluru, Karnataka.

http://cogwave.in/

Jun 2016 – Jul 2017

Software Engineer, Sivasakthi Software Services Pvt. Ltd, Coimbatore, Tamilnadu.

http://sivasakthisoft.com/

Jul 2014 - May 2016

Page | 1 Rajesh Sivasankaran

PROJECTS

Project Name	Primus
Duration	Aug 2017 – Till
Team size	5
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC & WebApi2
	HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery
	Angular 5
Role	Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Service & Bug Fixing
	Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	HMS (Hotel Management System)
Duration	Apr 2017 – Jul 2017
Team size	2
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC 5 & WebApi2
	Dapper ORM & Autofac
	Kendo UI
	HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Service & Bug Fixing & Stored Procedures
	Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	eKOT – POS
Duration	Mar 2017 – Apr 2017
Team size	2
Technologies	ASP.Net WebApi 2
	Dapper ORM & Autofac & Fluent Validation
	Angular 2 & Ionic 2 & TypeScript & Cordova
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	Design UI & Service & Bug Fixing
	Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	House Keeping - HMS (Hotel Management System)
Duration	Feb 2017 – Mar 2017
Team size	3
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC 5 & WebApi2
	Dapper ORM & Autofac
	HTML & Material CSS & JavaScript & jQuery
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Server Code & Bug Fixing & Stored Procedures
	Coordinated all updates with TFS

Page | 2 Rajesh Sivasankaran

Project Name	Online Reporting - HMS (Hotel Management System)
Duration	Jan 2017 – Feb 2017
Team size	3
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC 5 & WebApi2
	Dapper ORM & Autofac
	HTML & Material CSS & JavaScript & jQuery
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Code Development & Bug Fixing
	Stored Procedures
	Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	HIS (Hospital Information System)
Duration	Jul 2016 – Dec 2016
Team size	5
Technologies	ASP.Net WebApi2
	Dapper ORM & Autofac & Fluent Validation
	Angular 2 & TypeScript & HTML & Bootstrap CSS
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Code Development & Bug Fixing
	Stored Procedures
	Coordinated all updates with TFS

Project Name	SS KOT
Duration	Feb 2016 – May 2016
Team size	2
Technologies	ASP.Net WebApi2 & Entity Framework ORM
	HTML & CSS & JavaScript & Cordova
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	UI & Code Development & Bug Fixing

Project Name	Chit Fund Management
Duration	Jul 2015 – Feb 2016
Team size	4
Technologies	ASP.Net MVC & Entity Framework ORM & Dev Express
	HTML & CSS & JavaScript & jQuery
	MS SQL Server
Role	Full Stack Developer
Responsibilities	Database and Coding & Code Review
	Reporting with Team Leader
	Bug Fixing and Coordinated all updates

Page | 3 Rajesh Sivasankaran

Project Name	Finance/Accounts Maintenance
Duration	Jul 2014 – Jul 2015
Team size	5
Technologies	VB.Net
	Dev Express
	MS SQL Server
Role	Developer
Roles &	Reporting with Team Leader
Responsibilities	Bug Fixing
	Coordinated all updates
	Custom module development
	Customer Support

EDUCATION

Master Of Computer Applications (MCA)

2011 - 2014

Bachelor Of Computer Applications (BCA)

2008 - 2014

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

2006 - 2008

Secondary School Leaving Certificate (SSLC)

2006

Page | 4 Rajesh Sivasankaran